# **James Thomas Edmondson-Jones**

The Old Chapel Main Street Grasby, Lincolnshire DN38 6AH 07592533754

A graduate of Hull University with a BSc (Hons) in Computer Science. Experienced with learning and applying new skills, presenting information in a formal manner and working to set deadlines.

### **Employment History:**

**Deliveroo Rider (Hull Area)** 

January 2017 – September 2017 Salary: £5760 per annum pro rata

**Key roles and responsibilities**: Duties including collecting orders from specified restaurants, finding a safe and quick cycling route to the customer, cycling that route then finding the correct house or

office and delivering the order.

Reason for leaving: Moved out of area

#### **Research Assistant**

**September 2014 – July 2015** 

Sheffield Hallam University Howard Street Sheffield South Yorkshire

**S1 1WB** 

Salary: £19,500 per annum pro rata

**Key roles and responsibilities**: Duties included the daily preparation of the metabolic kitchen and ensuring the sensory laboratory was prepared ready for the commencement of the research study. Delivering inductions to research participants and ensuring the completion of Visual Analogue Scales and Profile of Mood State (POMS) questionnaires. I also designed a database for the collection and storage of research data

Reason for leaving: Fixed term contract and move to Hull

#### **Library/IT Assistant**

January 2012 - September 2014

Caistor Arts and Heritage Centre 28 Plough Hill Caistor

LN7 6LZ

Lincolnshire

Salary: Volunteer

**Key roles and responsibilities**: Duties included supervising the library as the only member of staff during the early evening period. The cataloguing of returned books using the library systems. Assisting members of the public in using the computer suite, tailoring my support and training based on the individual requirements of the customer. Dealing with requests and queries on a range of technical and IT related issues.

Reason for leaving: revision for A levels

## **Education**

2:1 BSc (Hons)	Computer Science	Hull University	2018
A Level Grade C	Geography	Caistor Grammar	2015
A Level Grade C	ICT	Caistor Grammar	2015
A Level Grade D	Physics	Caistor Grammar	2015
A Level Grade D	General Studies	Caistor Grammar	2015
13 GCSE (A-C)	Including English,	Caistor Grammar	2013
	Maths, Physics, Biology,		
	Chemistry and ICT		

# **Other Qualifications/Achievements**

- 2015 Laboratory Health & Safety Induction Sheffield Hallam University
- 2014 Data Protection West Lindsey Council
- 2014 Basic Health & Safety West Lindsey Council
- 2012 to 2014 Duke of Edinburgh Awards, Bronze, Silver & Gold
- 2013 National Citizenship Scheme
- 2011 National Science Competition

# **Interests**

I am a hiker having completed all three levels of Duke of Edinburgh Award. I have been a member of a rowing club from the age of 14; enjoy playing rugby and clay pigeon shooting. I have recently enjoyed supporting a Doctoral research project in the sensory laboratories of Sheffield Hallam University.

# Personal details

Date of birth: 11.10.1996